ROSIKIN

Cirebon, Jawa Barat 45191 | 089654857415 | rosikinrosikin120@gmail.com

https://s.id/rosikin portofolio website

Personal Profile

Data enthusiast with 1-year experience in the data related field. Familiar with ETL, Automation, Data Warehousing, Data pipeline architecture, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and Data Visualization. Having experience working in Startup and internships as a data engineer also having good analytical, problem-solving, and communication skills, and being able to work independently or in a team.

Education

Bachelor Of Computer Informatics Engineering

STMIK IKMI CIREBON Oct 2020 - Present GPA: 3,64/4,0

Participate training certifications:

- IT Essentials and CCNAv7 Introductions to Network (Cisco Networking Academy)
- Programming Essentials in Phyton (Phyton Academy)
- Database Design and Java Fundamentals (Oracle Academy)
- Data Management Staff (Indonesian Proffesional Certification Authority)
- Learn Machine Learning Beginners (Dicoding)
- Independent Study Certified Internship Batch 3 (Kampus Merdeka)

Work Experience

Data Engineer Intern PT. baracipta Esa Engineering

Aug 2021 - Dec 2022

- Perform Web Scraping to extract certain information from multiple websites
- Create Automate Scraping to multiple websites that can be fully automate with scheduler or automating tools
- Create Asynchronous Scraping to collect data from website that speed up running time up-to 2x faster from conventional scraping
- Create a project database structure
- Create multiple dashboards analyzing new your market and new your competitors, for company analysis
- Bypass the normal captcha for scraping on certain websites

Organizational Experience

Ikmi Cirebon Robotic Team (Member)

Jan 2021 - Dec 2020

- Managed to run 85% the work program
- Contribute to the Internet Of Things Kopertip Communication and Creativity Contest
- Contribute to the Internet Of things Techno Competion Corner Organized by Gadjah Mada University

Skills

Languages

: • Python

• SQL

. 6. . 6

• R

Tools

: • Google Colaboratory

- MySQL
- Office Family

- Jupyter Notebook
- Oracle
- Power BI